NGOYTRY LYHUOR





I am a flexible, trustworthy, self-motivated and hardworking person and my education has been excellent since I was a high school student and continues to this day. I want to get the opportunity from this job to develop myself better because my goal is to become the most professional and talented webmaster in the future.

HARD SKILLS

	_ D	ഥവ
•	Р	пΡ

- Laravel
- My SQL
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- iQuery

- C / C++
- HTML
- CSS
- Vue JS
- React JS
- Microsoft Office

SOFT SKILLS

- Communicate
- Creative thinking
- Motivate people

- Team work
- Positive thinking
- Imagination

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2023 - PRESENT

Intern, DATA ENTRY, APLUS CONSULTING CO. LTD

- Input information to Google Drive / Database.
- Keep review in Dashboard.
- Write formula to build some option in Database.
- Keep learning about Database and Dashboard.

MAR 2022 - MAR 2023

INSTRUCTOR, ETEC CENTER (IT)

 Teaching how write Microsoft Word, How to make Microsoft Excel formula and How to Make perfect Microsoft Powerpoint.

- Teaching fundamental of information technology (IT) language such as C programming , C++ programming and OOP .
- Teaching fundamental of Web frontend language such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript and jQuery.
- Teaching fundamental of Web backend language such as PHP, AJAX, Laravel and MYSQL.
- Teach and advise at least 100 students.

2021 - 2022

INSTRUCTOR, NEW INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY NIT (NIT)

- Teaching fundamental of Web frontend language such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript and jQuery.
- Teach and advise at least 50 students.

EDUCATION

2020 - PRESENT

BACHELOR DEGREE OF IMFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (IT)

Industrial Teachnical Institute (ITI)

2017 - 2020

GENERAL EDUCATION CERTIFICATE (BACII)

Kampong Chheuteal High School (KCIT)

LANGUAGE

Khmer : Mother Tongue English : Communication